{
    "subject": "resource/A_Little_Princess_(1995_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicComposer",
    "object": "resource/Patrick_Doyle",
    "human_readable": "The music composer of the 1995 film 'A Little Princess' is Patrick Doyle.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9015757441520691,
            "question": "Name the composer of the soundtrack for 'A Little Princess'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8966743350028992,
            "question": "Besides 'A Little Princess', what other films has Patrick Doyle composed music for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.887151837348938,
            "question": "Who composed the music for the film 'A Little Princess'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201501369476318,
            "question": "What is Patrick Doyle known for composing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5404456853866577,
            "question": "What genre of music is often associated with Patrick Doyle's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4523496627807617,
            "question": "What year was the film 'A Little Princess' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4414863884449005,
            "question": "What makes the music in 'A Little Princess' memorable?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3283594846725464,
            "question": "How does the music contribute to the overall story and atmosphere of 'A Little Princess'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32364514470100403,
            "question": "Is Patrick Doyle associated with any famous film scores?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18003468215465546,
            "question": "Has Patrick Doyle won any awards for his film scores?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music composer of the 1995 film 'A Little Princess' is Patrick Doyle.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6290_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Patrick Doyle associated with any famous film scores?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6290_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the music contribute to the overall story and atmosphere of 'A Little Princess'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6290_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes the music in 'A Little Princess' memorable?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6290_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6290_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query asks whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"The music composer of the 1995 film 'A Little Princess' is Patrick Doyle.\"\n\nThe relevant document for this question is:\n\nfile_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6290/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt\n\nQuick facts for kids\n\n...\n\nMusic by Patrick Doyle ...\n\nThis document directly states that the music composer of the 1995 film \"A Little Princess\" is indeed Patrick Doyle.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Music by Patrick Doyle\" for the film \"A Little Princess,\" which confirms that Patrick Doyle is indeed the music composer of the 1995 film 'A Little Princess.'"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}